Amanda Steele shows. Now each week I'll keep you up to date on the shadiest bills or positive
policies being passed by state legislators with our new segment State of the State and today we
are going to Virginia. So an all-white school board in Virginia's Shenandoah County voted
five to one to restore the names of two schools previously honoring confederate leaders. Wow.
And then one of the board members emphasized that the decision was not based on race but
on rectifying past actions and restoring trust in authorities. They literally said that they are
emphasizing the importance of honoring community heritage. At the end of the day confederacy were
traitors against the United States. Now you have statues and schools named after you. All of that
correct but this is why local politics are essential. We need more representation and people who think
like supreme on these school boards and when we're on there we should keep that same energy. Welcome
to Nat Turner Elementary School. We have the Malcolm X debate team in the Tupac Glee Club. Students
will be performing powerful renditions of Brenda's Got a Baby and Ambitions of a Rider.
And I can't deny it. I'm a straight rider. You don't want to win me. Yeah, I want to hear it. I want to hear it.
We are.